stage.com 2019-12-08

# Privacy Policy l Stage Stores

Last Updated August 2, 2019.

This Privacy Policy applies to the information we receive in our retail store locations, including our Gordmans’ locations, through the operation of our Sites listed below, social media, blog, promotional alerts (text and voice communications), mobile apps and e-mail communications. In this policy, you can expect to learn about the information we may ask for you to provide to us and information that we may receive from third parties. Our full Privacy Policy is part of our User Agreement, and together they form a contract between you and Stage. Read our _Full Policy_ or scroll down.

Information We Collect

The information that you share with Stage allows us to provide you with a positive shopping experience by making it easier for you to find the products you need and want. We collect information from you when you provide it to us, when you interact with us online, visit our retail locations, download our mobile app, opt-in to receive marketing communications from us, participate in a survey, sweepstakes or one of our customer loyalty or discount programs, or apply for or use a Stage Credit Card (as defined below).

We collect this information in a variety of ways, including from web forms and technologies like cookies. We may combine the information we collect from you with information obtained offline and from other sources to help us improve its overall accuracy better tailor our interactions with you.

_Read more about Information We Collect_

How We Use Your Information

We use your information to provide you Stage products and services, or respond to your inquiries. We may disclose your information to third parties under the following circumstances:

We use your information to provide you Stage products and services, or respond to your inquiries. We may disclose your information to third parties under the following circumstances

  * with service providers or suppliers that help with our business operations or joint products;

  * with your consent; and

  * when necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of Stage, our customers, or when otherwise required by law.

_Read more about How We Use Your Information_

Your Choices

You may choose to stop receiving certain promotional communications by following instructions in those communications or by adjusting communication preferences by logging into your account and editing your marketing preferences.

We use interest-based advertising based on your browsing history. Review our full policy to learn about these ads and how to opt-out.

_Read more about Your Privacy Choices_

How To Contact Us

Questions about this Privacy Statement or about Stage’s handling of your information may be sent to:

[customercomments@stage.com](mailto:customercomments@stage.com) or

_Stage_

Attention: Privacy Office c/o Legal Department

2425 West Loop S, 11th Floor

Houston, Texas 77027

_Read more about Stage Privacy Policy_

##  _**STAGE PRIVACY POLICY – FULL POLICY**_

This Privacy Policy applies to information we receive through Specialty Retailers, Inc.’s: retail store locations (“Stores”), including Bealls, Goody’s, Gordmans, Palais Royal, Peebles and Stage (the five nameplates are collectively referred to as “Stage”); websites **[ beallstx.com](http://beallstx.com/)** , **[ goodysonline.com](http://goodysonline.com/)** , **[ gordmans.com](https://www.gordmans.com/)** , **[ palaisroyal.com](http://palaisroyal.com/)** , **[ peebles.com](http://peebles.com/)** , **[ stage.com](https://stage.com/)** , **[ blog.stage.com](https://stage.com/)** , **[ stagestores.com](https://www.stage.com/)** , and **[ stagestoresinc.com](http://www.stagestoresinc.com/)** (collectively referred to as “Sites”); social media pages, including Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest and LinkedIn (collectively referred to as “Social Media”); promotional messages delivered via text and voice (“Alerts”); Apple and Google mobile apps (“Mobile Apps”); and e-mail. The services that we provide in Stores and through our Sites, Mobile Apps, Social Media and Alerts are collectively referred to as “Services.”

Our full Privacy Policy is part of our User Agreement, and together they form a contract between you and Stage. By using or accessing the Service, you consent to our collection, use and sharing of your information and data, and other activities, as described below.

_Information We Collect_

**Information You Give Us.** We collect personal information from you in a variety of ways when you interact with Stage, both in our retail store locations and online. Some examples are when you:

  * _Create an account on our Sites;_

  * _Make an online or in-store purchase, return or exchange;_

  * _Purchase an electronic gift card;_

  * _Use our online order tracking;_

  * _Sign up to receive promotional emails;_

  * _Sign up to receive Text and Voice Promotional Alerts;_

  * _Sign up to join a loyalty, rewards or similar program or club;_

  * _Provide your contact information and product preferences in consulting with our beauty associates;_

  * _Participate in our surveys or focus groups;_

  * _Register to win prizes in our sweepstakes or contests;_

  * _Provide online product reviews;_

  * _Submit a request to our Customer Service team;_

  * _Apply for, and/or maintain, a Stage’s or Gordmans Credit Card;_

  * _Use and navigate Sites, including features to find store locations;_

  * _Interact with us on Social Media; and_

  * _Connect to the Wi-Fi provided in select store locations._

_Information Collected in Connection with Text and Voice Alerts._ For an explanation of the information that we collect in connection with operation of Text and Voice Alerts, please review the ** Text and Voice Promotional Alerts Terms and Conditions** .

**Information Collected Automatically.** Stage and its service providers may use technology to automatically collect information when you visit our Sites, view our emails, or interact with us on Social Media. The information collected may include Internet Protocol (IP) address, the type of mobile device you use, your device operating system and browser type, a unique device identifier, the address of a referring websites, the path you take through our Sites, and other information about your session on our Sites and Social Media pages. This information may be collected from you by means of cookies, pixel tags (also called web beacons or clear gifs), local shared objects and other technologies. Cookies allow us to recognize you as you when you use our Service or visit our Sites. A cookie is a small text file that a website or email may save to your browser and store on your hard drive. Local shared objects (“LSOs”) are also known as flash cookies. Cookies allow us to provide you relevant information as you use or return to our Sites. Some of this information may be linked to you personally. However, the information stored in a cookie cannot be used to personally identify you unless combined with information that you have provided in connection with a registration or purchase, or when choosing to sign up for promotional emails or contests. Pixel tags let us know if a website page was visited, an email was opened, or if ad banners on our websites, emails, and other sites were effective. We use the information collected through cookies, LSOs and pixel tags to provide a continuous and more personalized shopping experience for you, ensure that our Sites and Services work correctly, prevent fraud, support our customer marketing initiatives, and to provide us with analytics that help us enhance our Services, and determine your imprecise location (i.e., location derived from an IP address) when you open an email to serve you a relevant ad within that email. These third parties may receive anonymous information about your browsing and buying activity on our Sites. If you do not want your information used by these third parties, you can change the settings of your browser to reject cookies. See “Your Choices” below for more information.

_**Other Information We Obtain.** We may receive information about you from other sources and third parties. For instance, we obtain information from service providers to enhance our existing customer information, such as improving the accuracy of the information we have about our customers. The information may include demographics (such as number of household members, age, and gender), segment data, and purchase preference information from public databases, social media platforms, data append services and others. We use this information to help us correct or supplement our records, improve the quality or personalization of our service to you, and prevent or detect fraud._

_**Security Cameras.** Our stores have video cameras for operational and security purposes. This information may be used to help us improve the design of our stores to better serve our customers. However, we do not use these cameras to identify you personally, except as required for security and fraud prevention purposes._

How We Use Your Information

_We use the information we collect for our business purposes. These include order or service fulfillment, marketing, loss and fraud prevention, public safety and legal functions. Some examples include:_

  * _Process returns, exchanges and discounts;_

  * _Register and service your online account;_

  * _Ship merchandise that you purchase online;_

  * _Confirm and track your orders;_

  * _Operate customer loyalty programs;_

  * _Respond to your customer service inquiries;_

  * _Source and offer the products you want;_

  * _Prevent fraud and bill your credit card for your purchases;_

  * _Customize your shopping experience;_

  * _Provide promotional emails communications to you, if you choose to receive them;_

  * _Provide promotional voice and/or text Alerts to you, if you choose to receive them;_

  * _Tell you about special events, sweepstakes, promotions, and surveys, if you have opted into receiving communications from us;_

  * _Improve our website design;_

  * _Conduct research and analysis; and_

  * _Comply with valid legal procedures, requirements, regulations or statutes._

_We may share information with third party service providers that perform services for us, such as:_

  * _Processing and delivering the orders that you place with us;_

  * _Communicate with you about the status of your order;_

  * _Register and service your account;_

  * _Administer customer loyalty programs, contests, sweepstakes, promotions, and surveys;_

  * _Send you information about our products, services, and promotions;_

  * _Respond to reviews, comments, or other feedback you provide us;_

  * _Help us personalize our service offerings, websites, mobile services, and advertising;_

  * _Help us improve your experience in our stores and through our websites and mobile services; and_

  * _Protect the security and integrity of our websites, mobile services, and our business._

**Credit Cards** Your Bealls, Goody’s, Gordmans, Palais Royal, Peebles or Stage credit cards (“Stage Credit Card”), are issued by Comenity Bank. We share customer information with Comenity Bank for the purpose of providing customer service, operating customer loyalty programs and as otherwise necessary for operation of the credit program. We may share your information with Comenity Bank prior to you applying with for a Stage Credit Card so that they can provide you with information and offers. If you apply for and/or make a purchase with your Stage Credit Card, the Comenity Bank Financial Privacy Policy and Online Privacy Policy and will apply. For more information, please see the Comenity Bank **[ Financial Privacy](https://d.comenity.net/stage/common/privacy/FinancialPrivacy.xhtml)** **** and **[ Online Privacy](https://d.comenity.net/stagestores/public/onlineprivacy/OnlinePrivacy.xhtml)** Policies:

**_Magazine Subscription Program_** : The magazine subscription program is operated by Magazine Reward Center, a division of Synapse Retail Ventures, Inc. When you sign-up for this program, we share your information with Magazine Reward Center so that they can fulfil your order. For your privacy rights when enrolling in the magazine subscription program, please review the **[ Synapse Retail Ventures Privacy Policy](http://srvprivacy.com/) .**

**eGift Cards** Are provided by CashStar. For more details, please review [ CashStar’s Privacy Policy](https://stagestoresgiftcards.cashstar.com/about/privacy_policy/) .

Products and Services Offered by Other Businesses: We will sometimes allow other businesses to make products or services available to our customers. When you purchase products or services from these other businesses we share your information with these businesses so that they can fulfill your purchase. When the use your information is governed by their privacy policy, we will provide you with product or program materials that provide you with a link to their privacy policy.

**_**Business Transfers**_ **:** **We may share information with our subsidiaries and affiliates for internal business purposes. We may also disclose or transfer all information collected in the event of a proposed or actual sale (including as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings), financing, merger, or any other change in control or ownership of Stage or any of its assets or divisions.

****Legal and Safety Obligations:** **We may share your information: (i) in response to a subpoena or other legal process or if in our good faith opinion such disclosure is required or permitted by law; (ii) at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; (iii) to protect or defend Stage or enforce other policies applicable to the Service, such as our User Agreement; (iv) to prevent or prosecute fraud or other crimes that occur in our stores or the Sites; or (v) to protect the personal safety or rights of an individual. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we may also use video captured in-store, IP addresses, mobile device identifiers or any other information we collect to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with copyright owners, internet service providers, wireless service providers or law enforcement agencies in our discretion. Such disclosures may be carried out without notice to you.

* * *

**_**Your Choices**_**

We use an opt-in standard for sending you voice and text messages, which means we will only do so with your express consent. We use an opt-out standard for email or for other communications, such as postal mail. Opt-out means we may contact you, but will stop upon your request (as described in “Your Choices” below). You may choose to:

  * Stop receiving marketing or promotional e-mails, voice and/or text Alerts;

  * Update and correct your personal information; and

  * Cancel your account.

You may request that we do these things or contact us with questions by:

  * Accessing your online account and updating your information;

  * Following instructions in the e-mail, direct mail, or voice or text communication you received from us;

  * Contacting one of our customer representatives at 1-800-743-8730 to provide your request and current contact information;

  * Sending a letter with your request and current contact information to: Stage, Attn: Privacy Office c/o Legal Department, 2425 West Loop S, Houston, Texas 77027.

  * Sending us an e-mail at _[customercomments@stage.com](mailto:customercomments@stage.com)_

Even if you have opted out of receiving marketing communications, we may still contact you with questions or information regarding your order (such as regarding order status, shipment, or refunds) or to respond to your customer service requests.

Additionally, these standards may not apply to Stage Credit Card offerings because these are provided through Comenity Bank. However, you can choose to stop receiving certain prescreened offers of credit that originate from participating nationwide credit reporting agencies, including our prescreened offers, by calling the official Consumer Credit Reporting Industry organization at 1-888-567-8688 or by going to _[ www.optoutprescreen.com](http://www.optoutprescreen.com/)_ .

You may control the automatic collection of information by:

****Disabling Cookies.** **Most web browsers allow you to exercise control over cookie files on your computer by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying you when such a file is stored. However, if you disable cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of certain features of our site such as storing your shopping bag for a future visit and providing a more personalized experience. You may also change the settings of your browser to reject cookies. Each browser is different, so check your browser’s "Help" menu to learn how to update your cookie preferences.

****Blocking LSOs.** **If you do not want LSOs stored on your computer, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block LSO storage using the tools contained in the website storage settings panel. For help with managing LSOs please see Adobe’s help page . Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of LSOs may reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications, including, potentially, Flash applications used in connection with the Services or our online content.

****Managing Interest-Based Advertising Preferences.** **We personalize your experience on our sites and mobile services by showing you advertisements that are tailored to your interests. To help us do this, we belong to ad networks that may use your browsing history across participating websites and mobile services to show you interest-based advertisements. For example, if you browse or shop for electronics with us or on other sites, we may show you ads for electronics as you continue to browse the Internet. Information collected by our ad networks or other third-party service providers across multiple websites that you visit may enable the ad network to predict your preferences and show you ads that are most likely to be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive online behavioral advertising from us on other websites, please visit the _[ Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)_ . You may also visit the _[ Digital Advertising Alliance Consumer Choices Page](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers/)_ to learn about online behavioral advertising and how to opt-out from online behavioral ads served by some or all participating companies. These opt-out mechanisms rely on cookies to remember your choices with respect to ad-serving on websites. If you delete your cookies, use another computer or device, or change browsers, you will need to repeat this process. We are not responsible for effectiveness of, or compliance with, any third-parties’ opt-out options or programs or the accuracy of their statements regarding their programs. We may serve ads on or through third party services, such as Google and Facebook, that are targeted to reach people (or similar people) that have visited our Service or that are also identified in one of more of our databases (“Matched Ads”). This is done by us uploading certain of our data to the third party service, such as through Google Customer Match, and the third party service matching common factors against our data. To opt-out of such advertising, please contact the applicable third party service. We are not responsible for such third party service’s failure to comply with your opt-out instructions.

We may serve ads on or through third party services, such as Google and Facebook, that are targeted to reach people (or similar people) that have visited our Service or that are also identified in one of more of our databases (“Matched Ads”). This is done by us uploading certain of our data to the third party service, such as through Google Customer Match, and the third party service matching common factors against our data. To opt-out of such advertising, please contact the applicable third party service. We are not responsible for such third party service’s failure to comply with your opt-out instructions.

****Other Options.** **We also use Adobe and Google analytics to monitor performance and to better understand how our customers navigate the Sites. These services use cookies to track customer behavior online. You can opt-out of _[ Adobe Analytics](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/opt-out.html)_ __ and you can opt-out of tracking by _[ Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) ._

* * *

**Other Important Information**

**Security.** We maintain reasonable and appropriate physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality of personal information. While we work very hard to protect your privacy, no method of security is 100% effective. We make no warranties, express, implied or otherwise, as to the ultimate effectiveness of its reasonable and appropriate safeguards. We further disclaim, to the fullest extent of the law, any liability for any unauthorized access to, disclosure or damage to, interception of, theft, or loss of any data communications and/or personal information. By using the Services, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.

**Information from Children.** The Services are not geared towards children and we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of thirteen without parental consent. Please contact us if you believe your child may have provided us with information and you would like us to work to delete the information.

**Third Party Websites.** There may be hyperlinks contained in the Services, including this policy, to other websites or locations that are operated and controlled by third parties ("Third Party Websites"). These Third Party Websites may use their own cookies, web beacons and other technology to independently collect information about you. In addition, these Third Party Websites may solicit information from you. We make no representations regarding the policies or business practices of such Third Party Websites and encourage you to familiarize yourself with their privacy policies before providing them with your information.

**Your California Privacy Rights.** Once a year California customers may request a list of the categories of personal information shared with third parties for marketing purposes and a list of companies that we shared information with. To make this request, send an email or letter to us, note that it is a "California Privacy Rights Request," and provide your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code.

**Consent to Transfer Information.** The Services are operated in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, and are accessing or using the Service, please be aware that information we collect will be collected and stored in the United States. By using or accessing the Services or providing us with any information through the Services, you consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in United States.

**Social Media Features.** We may provide links or embed third party applications that allow you to visit of Social Media pages. These links or applications may allow you to login, post content or share information from our Social Media pages. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these third party services. Your use of these links and applications is subject to the third parties’ privacy policies, and you should become familiar with the third party sites' privacy policies before using them.

**Sweepstakes, Contests, and Promotions.** We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (each, a “Promotion”) that may require registration. If you choose to enter a Promotion, your Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties in connection with the administration of such Promotion, such as in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law, such as on a winners list. By entering a Promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor and/or other parties to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing materials. Stage may offer opportunities to enter a contest or sweepstakes or other feature that we offer jointly with a third party. As a result of your participation in such feature, your information may be shared with the third party that is jointly offering the feature, which will be disclosed at the time your information is collected.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy.** Stage may revise this Privacy Policy in the future. Changes will be effective immediately upon posting the revised policy, unless otherwise indicted in the updated policy. We will not use your information in a manner materially different than what was stated in the policy in effect at the time the information was collected unless we receive your consent. However, your continued use of the Services after posting the new policy may constitute consent.

****Contacting Us.** **If you have questions, suggestions, or complaints about this Privacy Policy or Stage’s privacy practices, send an email to _[ customercomments@stage.com](mailto:customercomments@stage.com)_ . You can also contact us by mail at the following postal address:

_Stage_

_Attn: Privacy Office c/o Legal Department_

_2425 West Loop S, 11th Floor Houston, Texas 77027_

**_**Electronic Communications.** _**When you subscribe to Alerts, text us, or send e-mails to us, you are communicating with us electronically. You consent to receive communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you by e-mail or by posting notices on this site or through the other Services. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.

ARBITRATION.

YOU AGREE THAT ALL DISPUTES, ACTIONS, AND CLAIMS RELATING IN ANY WAY TO OR ARISING OUT OF THESE TERMS AND/OR YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES (COLLECTIVELY “CLAIMS”) WILL BE GOVERNED BY THE FEDERAL ARBITRATION ACT, FEDERAL ARBITRATION LAW, AND LAWS OF THE STATE OF TEXAS, WITHOUT REGARD TO CHOICE OF LAW PRINCIPLES. YOU FURTHER AGREE THAT ALL CLAIMS WILL BE RESOLVED BY BINDING ARBITRATION, EXCEPT THAT YOU MAY ASSERT CLAIMS IN SMALL CLAIMS COURT IF YOUR CLAIMS QUALIFY. THE ARBITRATOR SHALL NOT CONSOLIDATE MORE THAN ONE USER’S CLAIMS, AND MAY NOT OTHERWISE PRESIDE OVER ANY FORM OF A REPRESENTATIVE, PRIVATE ATTORNEY GENERAL OR CLASS PROCEEDING. YOU ARE GIVING UP THE RIGHT TO LITIGATE ALL CLAIMS IN COURT BEFORE A JUDGE OR JURY. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, YOU AGREE THAT YOU WILL NOT ACT AS A REPRESENTATIVE OR A PRIVATE ATTORNEY GENERAL, OR IN ANY OTHER REPRESENTATIVE CAPACITY, OR PARTICIPATE AS A MEMBER OF A CLASS OF CLAIMANTS AGAINST STAGE IN ANY COURT, OR IN ARBITRATION, WITH RESPECT TO ANY CLAIMS. YOUR CLAIMS SHALL NOT BE JOINED TO ANY OTHER ARBITRATION OR DISPUTE INVOLVING ANY OTHER PARTY SUBJECT TO THESE TERMS, AND NO CLASS ARBITRATION PROCEEDINGS SHALL BE PERMITTED.

The arbitration will be conducted by the American Arbitration Association (AAA) under its rules, including the AAA's supplementary procedures for consumer-related disputes. The AAA's rules are available at www.adr.org or by calling 1-800-778-7879. You agree to commence arbitration only in your county of residence or in Harris County, Texas. You may choose to have the arbitration conducted by telephone, based on written submission, or in person by following the AAA rules. In a dispute involving $10,000 or less, any hearing will be telephonic unless the arbitrator finds good cause to hold an in-person hearing instead. The arbitrator may award the same damages to you individually as a court could.

_We will pay all administrative, hearing, and arbitrator’s fees and costs for the arbitration that are in excess of any filing fee that you would have been required to pay to file your Claims as a lawsuit in a state or federal court (whichever is greater). Unless the arbitrator awards otherwise, you will be responsible for paying the fees for your lawyers, witnesses (including experts), and all other expenses you incur. An arbitration award and any judgment confirming it apply only to that specific case. The arbitration award may be entered as a judgment only to enforce the award itself and cannot be used as evidence in any other case. To reduce the time and expense of the arbitration, the arbitrator will not provide a statement of reasons for his or her award unless requested to do so by all parties._

_Either party shall have the right to seek an injunction or other equitable relief related to infringement, violation, or a threat to infringe or violate the other party's patent, copyright, trademark or trade secret rights. The parties may seek such injunctive or other appropriate relief in any state or federal court in Harris County, Texas. You consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in Harris County, Texas._

**SURVIVAL; SEVERABILITY.** The arbitration provision of this Privacy Policy will survive the termination of the relationship between you and Stage. To the maximum extent possible, if any provision of these Terms shall be interpreted is deemed by any arbitrator or court of competent jurisdiction to be unlawful or unenforceable, it will not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions. Additionally, any unenforceable provision shall be deemed modified so as to be rendered valid and enforceable while implementing, to the greatest extent possible, the original intent of such provision.

Last Updated August 2, 2019.
